It's the fun left now, so to speak.
The motives and some text and these things that I should do.
Will still take eight ten hours anyway.
Yes, it will probably take this all day before it's done.
Although this time we'll probably try to pause a little in the middle of Dan
And have lunch so you don't get completely spinning in your head.
It's not a stupid idea.
Andreas works today.
Yes he is not there and I think that is great fun
And he will not come and look at the car until it is done.
No matter when he quits.
So it's very fun I think.
Do not have to drive otherwise.
You drive something really cool.
I think it's pretty cool.
Unfortunately there are very many who make very weird shark teeth
on the side of the car by type so far or something like that
Where you buy decal at Wish.
It is not very nice simply.
I think a lot in that you simply have to draw it up.
Why do you paint with chalk?
Then I get a temporary painting to begin with.
I want to be happy with what I do first.
Sketch up as well.
Just look at a picture for inspiration.
After all, it will be very own now.
Walking and painting straight on this?
Yes it does.
Then you just wipe off.
It can get a little messy sometimes, but do you have a lot of color
So then it is no problem to paint over chalk.
Spray or get that with pencil.
It will be mostly with a pen and possibly a little color.
I thought it should be some highlights with color with spray cans
And then it should be shaded around too.
But first I do these stuff now as well.
But I just pull the first lines now then that lime falls away.
Sitting so loosely.
How is the color sitting?
Sits as well as any.
As good as this color black in so that I buy replenishment.
Instead of buying new pens, I buy refill
Because you can change the cape.
And then you do this only when you have to change
Or replenish color just when the other direction so.
Then you pick off and pour down just here.
It's so good so you fill them.
You see the difference
here.
There is so little needed to really get it there.
You should have a mask huh?
Yes, now it was actually so that it was standing still here the air
Empty!
A shark always has teeth that are growing out.
And so that's why sitting in between.
That was not stupid.
It got cool.
And so gets the same on the other side?
It will be.
Yes, gray and gray and black.
Yes.
Where is pink?
And ketchup?
Ketchup is coming.
I have been waiting for ketchup.
Yes, I think like this if a shark has big fangs,
What is taken then?
You wear things in.
What then?
Blood.
Just right.
But it's like the Final Touch when you have chewed up the buns.
Yes, I have made a pickles, a Silverado 1500 from 2000 and a pretty big one too.
There was a lot to work on, but I did that completely differently.
It wasn't that I pulled such just lines
Without I made the whole body looked
as it was made in sheet metal.
We even sat real plates on all screen edges.
So they were really redone.
This one I came up with myself.
Many times I need when I drive toward edges
And stuff when I spray.
Then I just put it against spraying.
Especially when I did these who looked like plates on this chevan.
You use this all the time.
It was really sunny from the beginning as well as
The end result was really cool.
There I used all the imagination I had and some more.
But I thought I saw when you paint on some bus.
Yes, it is a new project.
It is a very good friend who has a bus he has done.
I drive over the mold so it looks great so it was actually really cool.
It looks really cool!
You can see the front here now, I drew after all
On the only thing I've done there as well.
But here I have done so that this dark green instead
And the other is light green on the outside.
It's a bit like that blink to Amazon actually,
Which has a barbecue six months.
I think it was pretty cool this.
It already looks a booklet on the hood so it doesn't matter.
It is not that it is not visible if we say so.
So now I drive with light gray.
It is a very nice color that goes well against this.
Yes, bright to the dark too so it as a shading.
The gray was black and now I run with this
That is an adaptation.
Oh, it ran a little.
Well what a nice thing I feel.
It doesn't make things uglier because they're not exact.
Straight Lines as well.
As you have driven with a fucking ruler as well.
If you want such stuff, you should not go to me, he says.
However, do you want stuff with a little more soul and improvisation
And as some say, a little more chaos, then it's fun to go to me.
How to get in touch with you?
I know you, though.
Just because it really doesn't cover over something
that is dangerous or something.
So that's really.
One cannot say that it is unauthorized drawing
Because then you don't look, yea right?
You can put decals anyway, but you can't pull
Some lines on a box.
It sounds totally sick.
So we'll see what they think.
Here in Lidköping.
It is going to be fun
This is ketchup when I spray on the brush
A good color when you want some effects.
Written on the rear screen.
Yes it sat.
Damn a lot of red color it will be here behind.
Yes it does nothing.
It sprays blood and jaws on them here.
What are you going to do now?
It is not possible to describe words that are just trying to bring in all this.
It's so damn awesome.
He has done good jobs.
I know he is good, but this is far beyond my expectation.
As I saw it yesterday.
I could never have imagined that.
The final result.
Now he is really customs that I wanted what I wanted it.
Now he lives up to my goal with it.
I am more than satisfied.
This is far above what I could have dreamed
about at all.
But now it is visible.
If it didn't do it before.
It's not raining away.
I've put it on.
Then it blew like that.
But it blew less on this page than the other.
When the sun is shining on it, it glitters on well.
It is one of those where one can stand and stare in a long time
And discover new things all the time.
Will be interesting to see them when we have our hits next Thursday
Exhibit it and see people's reaction.
Set me a little and let people react to it.
You will pick around tonight.